Why did the order explode again? Earn Haval coins directly! If you don’t betray your boss, why will the boss not see you?
This boss is probably going to send someone away to help me get older! I'll help you add brothers, where can I nod? backpack,
Throw down all the single items and I’ll give you some treasure, hurry, hurry, hurry! Don’t betray your boss,
If you leave the package list to my brother, you will die immediately! Sorry, what are you doing? Are you a pig? I'm stuck! Stuck!
Ouch!
Alas, the warehouse is out of money again, only 200,000 is left. I recently applied to a club,
When a thug goes in to make some money, Haval will definitely eat it. Hello, Hello, the boss is Mai Mai,
This is the sweetness of Niu Mullen, happy to serve you. Hello, boss, I’m Hululu,
It's a pleasure to serve you. You thug, oh, okay, okay, can you detect it? It can be measured.
Boss, boss, boss, look, look, look at the core area, we are here! I am a brother,
What the hell is that voice of yours! Holy shit!
Why didn't you bring a big bag? Then didn't you say you would bring it? I got stuck, I said I would bring it,
I just gave you this insurance, shouldn’t it be for me? Why did you, a thug, eat first? My account number is a Tangren account.
The package rate is high and you follow the boss. What kind of Tang list are you playing? I'm a murderous thug, what are you doing? Lulu,
What are you doing? Me, how do I get here? Boss, I'll help you add guns this morning. Holy shit! Killed with one shot,
How could you, a thug, be like this? I'll give the boss a cigarette, and you run back to carry your boss.
You're running the wrong way, you stupid pig! Running backwards! Running backwards! Oops, what does the boss do?
This boss won’t kill you! oops! Are you a stupid pig? You, a thug, don't even have any equipment.
You don't even have a bag, and you just lie down on the ground when you see someone. What are you doing? Your brother, don’t leave,
Let's fight again! Find someone else to call and give you a call! Old boss, don't leave.
Trust me again.
Hello, boss Wang, hello! Let Niu Ma Long click in here, come on,
It's a pleasure to serve you. Brother, give me a big red envelope! I brought one to my boss, okay.
I dragged the card out, holy shit, I clicked the wrong one! Why are you wearing a windbreaker? I ordered it wrong,
Sorry! You see, our place doesn’t smell like smoke, you know that, right? I smell smoke.
Isn’t the boss just playing like a hotel? Play better and don't cheat me! I'm Ma Yida, don't worry, don't let it go,
No, it smells really good! Why are you still walking behind the boss? I am the queen, brother!
I'm afraid someone will steal my boss.
Chrysanthemum, chrysanthemum adds some hair to me! I'll help you carry your brother, where's my headgear? Can I not grow up?
If you don’t have your headgear, give me a place here, and if there’s a fight over there, go and help me! Boss, don't give away people's heads.
Dude, give me back my headgear! Boss, give me some extra hair, I saw me! Big grass, big grass in one stroke!
Big grass, big grass! Brother, help me set up the gun and fight! I'm standing there, you take away my armor, and then you take my gun?
If you were Yang Luhu, I would fight you! Don't hit him!
Stop fucking around, man! You're going to take my head man away, and you're not going to help me in this fight. Look,
Hey, boss, who is this thug of yours? You've got it covered, go save the boss! Stop tearing the bag, okay?
Dude, you're going to kill me! I save! I save! I save! I save! I save! Brother, hurry up and save me!
I'll add a gun! I am coming! I'm a bit of a resurrection bag from this angle, my boss! I still messed with him!
Who is your thug? You thug! Dude, what are you doing? I’ll give you a boss gift package! Dude,
Are you the boss or is he the boss? Then you still want to grab your bag?
You brought this gun in to grab the bag? What kind of gun is this? This stuff isn't bad. Didn’t I hit him?
I am making a paper stand! You are playing a paper stand, and the two people on the other side have been charging at each other for so long, but you haven't fired a single shot?
What happened to your paper holder? There is no paper frame on the opposite side, what's the defense method? What gun? Are you tired, bro?
What does unlock bag mean? Did I forget to do it? I'll open it for you now. Thank you for your hard work, boss.
Eat.
Big boss, how much can I add? I'll bring you a pack. Well, okay, I haven't seen you fire a single shot either.
Dude! I believe in your strength, brother! We haven't finished the fight yet, 3.5 million now.
It shouldn’t be, let’s not fight, there are so many people! In my hand, give me the 250 to brother! Well, okay,
I dropped the 250 and looked to see if any of my teammates had dropped it. I must have remembered it wrong, right?
Then boss, you can take it. You can throw down your knife and I'll replace it directly. I'll replace it directly and give it to Brother. Well,
Okay, I have nothing. What are you carrying?
Ah, where did the huge waves come from? Oh, he probably gave this to you accidentally.
You put your big wave in your bag, Brother Lai, uh, I've finished it here, but you don't have anything there yet.
If you have something, give it to me. We have nothing left, please order it, we are ready to evacuate.
Okay, okay, my boss, who still has some golden eggs, throw down your backpack and hang it all.
I'll give you some golden eggs, hurry, hurry, hurry! Single hanging single hanging, boss, single hanging and single hanging boss,
My brother, my brother, please give it a try. Please pay attention to the time and try again later. Try again. I will try again, boss.
I tried it. Hey, you still have more than forty seconds to stop.
Hurry! Hurry! Twenty seconds left! There are still twenty seconds! Give it to me! What are you doing rolling around?
You don’t need to fuck anymore, you don’t need to fuck anymore, I’ll throw away your balls and give them to brother! I lost it to my brother!
It's done now! What are you doing? You are a pig! It's done now! What are you doing? What are you doing? Not included anymore,
Give it to me! It's stuck, give it to me! It's stuck, give it to me! Ouch! Are you here to get the box?
I am really angry with him now. I keep reminding you that you are not throwing away your bag. What do you mean? Brother,
What are you doing? I got stuck just now, did you catch the egg?
Take an order! You take the order, take the order, I take the order for you without firing a gun, what are you doing?
What on earth are you here for? Are you here to be a thug, or are you here to be the boss?
Are you here to torture me? You stupid pig! Thug! Well, brother, I'll take charge,
Sorry it's stuck, please give it another try! Who is fighting you? You, your management, tell me this!
It's okay, you Hululu, just wait for the after-sales service! What happened? Old aunt's head,
What am I doing?
Where did you get admitted from? Not carrying a bag for the boss, but also grabbing supplies from the boss.
Finally, we evacuated with the boss's equipment and seized it. Are you sick? Just wait!
Is your name Zhang Zihao? No, I'm not. You already knew my information.
Isn’t this news reviewed by some customer service team in the background? How come this information is from Nezha?